<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Matrix Bismuth Screensaver</string>
    <string name="my_daydream_name">Bismuth Matrix Screensaver</string>

    <!-- License -->
    <string name="app_license">
       MIT License

Copyright (c) 2021 DoNutsLise

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
    </string>

    <!-- help with settings -->
    <string name="helpCustomizationPreferencesString">
        1. Raining Code color:
            Choose the color of characters of the raining code.
        2. Raining code density:
            Number of columns of the raining code on the screen. the higher the number the more dense the raining code will appear. The default number is 25.
        3. Raining code speed:
            This parameter defines the speed of characters in the column (how fast the raining code falls). Default value is 50.
        4. Unlock "My Message" customization:
            This will allow you to define your own message. The words from your message will randomly appear in the raining code. You will have to complete a challenge to unlock this option.
        5. My Message in the raining code:
            Here you can define your own message. The words from your message will randomly appear in the raining code.
        6. Highlight my message:
            If enabled, the words from your message will be highlighted in the raining code with blue and purple colors.
        7. Use custom background image:
            You can choose an image stored on your phone as a background for raining code. Default background is black.
        8. Select background image:
            Click this preference to launch an image selection wizard.
        9. Background transparency:
            This parameter defines how clearly the image you chose for the background will be visible. The higher the value of the transparency the more clearly the image will be visible.
    </string>
</resources>